[NELLY FURTADO] AM I
THROWIN' YOU OFF?
[TIMBALAND] NOPE.
[NELLY FURTADO] DIDN'T THINK SO.
♪♪♪
♪ HOW YOU DOIN', YOUNG LADY ♪
♪ THAT FEELING THAT YOU GIVING
REALLY DRIVES ME CRAZY ♪
♪ YOU DON'T, HAVE A PLAYER
'BOUT TO CHOKE ♪
♪ I WAS AT A LOSS FOR WORDS
FIRST TIME THAT WE SPOKE ♪
♪ YOU LOOKIN' FOR A GIRL
THAT'LL TREAT YOU RIGHT ♪
♪ HOW YOU LOOKIN' FOR HER
IN THE DAYTIME WITH THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT BE THE TYPE
IF I PLAY MY CARDS RIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL FIND OUT BY THE END
OF THE NIGHT ♪
♪ YOU EXPECT ME
TO JUST LET YOU HIT IT ♪
♪ BUT WILL YOU STILL RESPECT ME
IF YOU GET IT ♪
♪ ALL I CAN DO IS TRY,
GIMME ONE CHANCE (CHANCE) ♪
♪ WHAT'S THE PROBLEM I DON'T SEE
NO RING ON YOUR HAND (HAND) ♪
♪ I'LL BE THE FIRST
TO ADMIT IT ♪
♪ I'M CURIOUS ABOUT YOU,
YOU SEEM SO INNOCENT ♪
♪ YOU WANNA GET IN MY WORLD,
GET LOST IN IT ♪
♪ BOY, I'M TIRED OF RUNNIN',
LET'S WALK FOR A MINUTE ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
WHEREVER YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ALL ALONE,
AND IT'S YOU THAT I WANT ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
YOU ALREADY KNOW ♪
♪ THAT I'M ALL YOURS,
WHAT YOU WAITING FOR ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
YOU'RE TEASIN' ME ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT,
AND I GOT WHAT YOU NEED ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
LET'S GET TO THE POINT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE ON A ROLL,
YOU READY ♪
♪ ROSES ARE RED,
SOME DIAMONDS ARE BLUE ♪
♪ CHIVALRY IS DEAD,
BUT YOU'RE STILL KINDA CUTE ♪
♪ HEY, I CAN'T KEEP
MY MIND OFF YOU ♪
♪ WHERE YOU AT, DO YOU MIND
IF I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I'M OUT OF THIS WORLD,
COME WITH ME TO MY PLANET ♪
♪ GET YOU ON MY LEVEL, DO YOU
THINK THAT YOU CAN HANDLE IT ♪
♪ THEY CALL ME THOMAS,
LAST NAME CROWN ♪
♪ RECOGNIZE GAME,
I'MA LAY MINE'S DOWN ♪
♪ I'M A BIG GIRL,
I CAN HANDLE MYSELF ♪
♪ BUT IF I GET LONELY,
I'MA NEED YOUR HELP ♪
♪ PAY ATTENTION TO ME,
I DON'T TALK FOR MY HEALTH ♪
♪ - I WANT YOU ON MY TEAM
- SO DOES EVERYBODY ELSE ♪
♪ SHH, BABY, WE CAN KEEP IT
ON THE LOW (LOW) ♪
♪ LET YOUR GUARD DOWN,
AIN'T NOBODY GOTTA KNOW (KNOW) ♪
♪ IF YOU WITH IT, GIRL,
I KNOW A PLACE WE CAN GO ♪
♪ WHAT KIND OF GIRL
DO YOU TAKE ME FOR ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
WHEREVER YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ALL ALONE,
AND IT'S YOU THAT I WANT ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
YOU ALREADY KNOW ♪
♪ THAT I'M ALL YOURS,
WHAT YOU WAITING FOR ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
YOU'RE TEASIN' ME ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT,
AND I GOT WHAT YOU NEED ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
LET'S GET TO THE POINT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE ON A ROLL,
YOU READY ♪
♪ DON'T BE MAD, DON'T GET MEAN ♪
♪ DON'T GET MAD, DON'T BE MEAN ♪
♪ HEY, DON'T BE MAD,
DON'T GET MEAN ♪
♪ DON'T GET MAD, DON'T BE MEAN ♪
♪ WAIT, I DON'T MEAN NO HARM ♪
♪ I CAN SEE YOU
WITH MY T-SHIRT ON ♪
WITH NOTHIN' ON ♪
♪ FEELIN' ON ME BEFORE
YOU BRING THAT ON ♪
♪ BRING THAT ON ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN ♪
♪ GIRL, I'M A FREAK,
YOU SHOULDN'T SAY THOSE THINGS ♪
♪ I'M ONLY TRYING TO GET INSIDE
OF YOUR BRAIN ♪
♪ TO SEE IF YOU CAN WORK ME
THE WAY YOU SAY ♪
♪ IT'S OKAY, IT'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ I GOT SOMETHING
THAT YOU GON' LIKE ♪
♪ HEY, IS THAT THE TRUTH
OR ARE YOU TALKING TRASH ♪
♪ IS YOUR GAME M.V.P
LIKE STEVE NASH ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
WHEREVER YOU ARE ♪
♪ I'M ALL ALONE,
AND IT'S YOU THAT I WANT ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
I'M CALLIN' YA NAME ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE DRIVIN' ME CRAZY
THE WAY YOU'RE MAKIN' ME WAIT ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS GIRL,
YOU'RE TEASIN' ME ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT,
AND I GOT WHAT YOU NEED ♪
♪ PROMISCUOUS BOY,
WE'RE ONE IN THE SAME ♪
♪ SO WE DON'T GOTTA PLAY GAMES
NO MORE ♪
♪♪♪